itqlick.com 2019-07-02

# ITQlick Privacy Policy - Read Inside | ITQlick

Last update: Sept, 2018.

You are being presented this Privacy Policy because you are visiting a website (the “Website”) that is either (a) owned and operated by IT Media Ltd. (“IT Media Ltd”, “IT Media, "ITQlick") or (b) includes content, including but not limited to registration and other forms, owned by IT Media Ltd or drawn from a website owned and operated by IT Media Ltd. IT Media Ltd is committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors' personally identifiable information. The following privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") explains our online information practices, use of the information you provide us and the choices you can make about the way your information is used by IT Media Ltd. By using the Website and providing personally identifiable information about yourself, you do hereby consent to (1) our Terms of Use, (2) our collection, use, and sharing of data as described in this Privacy Policy; (3) the notice, choice, access, and security we are providing, as described above; and (4) the methods we have described to notify you of changes to this Privacy Policy. 

SO THAT WE MAY ASSIST YOU WITH YOUR SOFTWARE LICENSING/PURCHASE INQUIRY, PLEASE BE ADVISED THAT IT Media Ltd WILL FURNISH THE INFORMATION YOU SUBMIT ON THE WEBSITE TO OUR PARTICIPATING SOFTWARE VENDORS SO THAT THEY MAY CONTACT YOU ABOUT THEIR PRODUCTS, SERVICES, OFFERS, AND PROMOTIONS. WHEN YOU DOWNLOAD ARTICLES OF INTEREST WRITTEN (IN WHOLE OR IN PART) BY ONE OF OUR GUEST AUTHORS (AN "ADVISOR"), IT Media Ltd WILL FURNISH THE INFORMATION YOU SUBMIT ON THE WEBSITE TO SUCH ADVISOR SO THAT HE/SHE MAY CONTACT YOU ABOUT THE SUBJECT MATTER OF THE ARTICLE.

IT Media may gather information about you from the Website and from other sources, such as information you provide to our affiliated companies, including affiliated websites (which may be owned and/or operated by persons having no ownership relationship with IT Media Ltd) or may be an entity directly or indirectly controlling, controlled by or under common control with IT Media Ltd ("Affiliates").

### Introduction:

The mission of ITQlick is to help software buyers find the right software for their organization. To achieve our Mission, we make services available through our website.  
Being part of ITQlick means sharing information about yourself with other professionals, communicating with them, as well as working privately on your own. By default, your account is set up to share the information that we have found the vast majority of our Users are interested in sharing. But the amount and type of information you decide to share, and with whom you share it, is up to you.  
Here are the purposes in which we may collect certain personally identifiable information from you :  

  * Communication with other users: We help you communicate with connections, companies and other professionals. Some of this is one-to-one, some of it is in groups, and some of it is public discussion.  You decide how much or how little you wish to communicate to individuals or groups.
  * providing information to us, to owners/operators of affiliate Websites, and/or to the vendor(s) of the software product(s) which you express an interest in purchasing or licensing so that we can contact you and help initiate contact and establish communication between you and such vendor(s) or Affiliates.
  * providing information to an Advisor whose article you have specifically requested to download.
  * conducting other transactions offered by IT Media that you may request.
  * assisting us in providing better products and services (for example, we may contact you to assist us in evaluating the performance of our staff, to assess the quality of product and service received and to help us improve the Website and our facilities and services).
  * compiling and aggregating statistics and analyses about users' use of the Website, products and services, which statistics are used to enable us to provide better service and products to you and others in the future.

Information we may collect:  

  * Information about yourself that you share: This is the information that your connections, other professionals, and companies see about you. This includes your profile, projects you post, companies and products you follow and your contributions to discussions on ITQlick, Questions, Answers, or other community features which, if you choose to opt-in, can show you who viewed your profile (and will show others when you visited their profiles).  You have control over what you share, and you can update information at any time.
  * names
  * physical addresses
  * telephone numbers
  * e-mail addresses
  * information regarding your business (e.g., business name, revenue thresholds, etc.)
  * information regarding your business needs and software requirements
  * all other personally identifiable information you affirmatively provide to us.

We reserve the right to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the top and/or bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. If you object to any changes, you may [close your account](https://www.itqlick.com/Close). By continuing to use the ITQlick service after notice of changes has been sent to you or published on the ITQlick website, you are consenting to the changes.  

Please read this policy and [send us](https://www.itqlick.com/) questions, concerns and suggestions.  

### What ITQlick’s Privacy Policy Covers:

1\. Information collected by ITQlick.  
2\. How ITQlick uses your information.  
3\. Your information choices.  
4\. Your obligations as a User.  
5\. Important information regarding service eligibility.  
6\. Security.  
7\. Your European Privacy Rights Under GDPR.  
8\. How to contact us.  

### 1\. Information Collected

The mission of ITQlick is to help software buyers find the right software for their organization. To achieve our Mission, we make services available through our website. information provided as part of the ITQlick services (“Services”) to enable professionals to develop, maintain and enhance a network of contacts, seek experts and consultants, fill job opportunities, create, share, and distribute information in collaboration with one another. By joining ITQlick, you voluntarily and willingly provide ITQlick Corporation in Tel Aviv, Israel, certain information, including personally identifiable information, which we collect in order to provide the Services. If you have any hesitation about providing information to us and/or having your information displayed on the ITQlick website or otherwise used in any manner permitted in this Privacy Policy and the User Agreement, you should not become a member of the ITQlick community; and, if you are already a member, you should close your account.  
We collect your personal information in the following ways:  

#### A. Registration:

In order to become a User, you must provide us the following information to create an account: name, email address, and password. Without this minimal amount of information, you cannot create an ITQlick account. Like other passwords, you should choose one that is known only by you. ITQlick requests other information from you during the registration process, (e.g., location, etc.) that ITQlick uses to provide better, more customized services such as language-specific profile pages and updates, better ads, and more valuable career opportunities. You acknowledge that this information is personal to you, and by creating an account on ITQlick, you allow others, including ITQlick, to identify you and to allow LI to use your information in accordance with our 

 _[Terms of Service](https://www.itqlick.com/Terms)_

.

#### B. Profile Information:

Once you become a User, you may provide additional information to your ITQlickProfiledescribing your skills, professional experiences, educational background, products you work with, recommendations and feedback from other ITQlick Users, group memberships, and networking objectives (among other options). Providing additional information about yourself beyond what is minimally required at registration is entirely up to you, but providing additional information enables you to derive more benefit from ITQlick and your professional network by helping you build your professional identity and leverage your professional network and facilitating your search for professional resources, information, and new opportunities. Any information you provide at registration or in the Profile section may be used by ITQlick as described in the 

 _[Terms of Service](https://www.itqlick.com/Terms)_

 and this Privacy Policy, including for the purpose of allowing professional opportunities to find you on ITQlick, or for serving more relevant advertisements on ITQlick. Learn more about ITQlick’s advertising practices by reading this privacy policy, in particular Sections 1.H, 2.J, and 2.K. If you decide not to share certain information, you may not receive the full benefit of being an ITQlick User.

#### C. Contacts Information:

In order to connect with others on ITQlick, you may use the Services to send invitations either to their ITQlick profiles or email addresses of people you know if they have not registered with ITQlick. The names and email addresses of people whom you invite will be used to send your invitations and reminders as well as to allow ITQlick to help expand your network. Please note that when you send an invitation to connect to another User, that User will have access to your email address because it is displayed in the invitation. Your ITQlick connections will also have access to your email address. You may not invite anyone you do not know and trust to connect with you.  
By providing email addresses or other information of non-Users to ITQlick, you represent that you have authority to do so. All information that you enter or upload about your contacts is covered by the User Agreement and this Privacy Policy and will enable us to provide customized services such as suggesting people to connect with on ITQlick.

#### D. Customer Service:

We collect information when you interact with ITQlick’s 

 _[customer service](https://www.itqlick.com/)_

in order to accurately categorize and respond to customer inquiries and investigate breaches of our terms.

#### E. Using the ITQlick Site and Applications

We receive information when you interact with and use the ITQlick website, ITQlick Applications (e.g. ITQlick for iPhone, Android, etc.), and ITQlick platform technology. For example, we know when you click on ads, upload your address book, join groups or projects, participate in polls, install an ITQlick mobile application, share articles on ITQlick, etc.

#### F. Using Third Party Services and Visiting Third Party Sites

We receive information when you use your ITQlick account to log in or authenticate to a third-party website or application. Also, if you are logged into ITQlick and visit a third party site that embeds ITQlick professional plugins, like “Share on ITQlick” for web publishers, ITQlick will receive information that those pages have loaded in your web browser. ITQlick will use this information to personalize the ITQlick-provided functionality, including providing you insights from your ITQlick network, allowing you to share information with your network, enabling you to use ITQlick functionality off the ITQlick site and serving you more relevant advertising.

#### G. Cookies

Like most websites, we use cookies and web log files to track site usage and trends, to improve the quality of our service, to customize your experience on ITQlick, as well as to deliver ITQlick and third-party advertising to Users both on and off the ITQlick site. A cookie is a tiny data file that resides on your computer, mobile phone, or other device, and allows us to recognize you as a User when you return to the ITQlick website using the same computer and web browser. You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser, but in some cases doing so may impact your ability to use ITQlick. One type of cookie, known as a “persistent” cookie, is set once you’ve logged in to your ITQlick account. The next time you visit the ITQlick website, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing User so you will not need to log in before using the Services. In order to access or change any of your private information or to send a message to another User, however, you must log in securely again with your password even if your computer contains your persistent cookie. Another type of cookie, called a “session” cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the ITQlick website. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser. Other technology like Macromedia’s flash can be used to place the functional equivalent of a cookie on your computer. You can control flash “local stored objects” or “flash cookies” using the Macromedia Website Privacy Settings Panel at www.macromedia.com. ITQlick may use cookie-equivalent technology for the limited purpose of enhancing the security of ITQlick's services. We do not use flash cookies for advertising purposes.  
In the course of serving advertisements or optimizing the Services to our Users, we may allow authorized third parties to place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Any information provided to third parties through cookies will not be personally identifiable but may provide general segment information (e.g., your industry or geography, career field, or information about your professional or educational background) for the enhancement of your user experience by providing more relevant advertising. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. ITQlick does not store unencrypted personally identifiable information in the cookies.

#### H. Advertising and Web Beacons

To support the Services we provide at no cost to our Users, as well as provide a more relevant and useful experience for our Users, we target and serve our own ads and third-party ads both on and off the site using ad networks. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad exchanges, ad technology vendors and research firms.  
We target ads to Users based on general profile categories (e.g., “product managers in new york”) or on non-personally identifiable information inferred from a User’s profile (e.g., industry, current or former company, products, school, compensation bracket, gender, age, ethnic origin, nationality, or other aspects of your life) in addition to a User’s use of ITQlick or their clicking on ITQlick ad inventory. ITQlick does not provide personally identifiable information to any third party ad network.  
We use ad technology such as web beacons, pixels, anonymous ad network tags, and cookies to more effectively serve ads to our Users on and off ITQlick through ad networks, as well as to collect anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for advertisers. Because your web browser requests advertisements and web beacons directly from ad network servers, these networks can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.  
You may opt-out of ads served to you off ITQlick. If you opt-out you may lose certain functionality of the ITQlick Services, as well as the potential benefit of receiving ads that are targeted to your interests which, in turn, may limit your ability to fully realize the benefits of the ITQlick Services to build and leverage your professional network.

#### I. Log files, IP Addresses and information about your computer and mobile device

Due to the communications standards on the internet, when you visit the ITQlick website we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave ITQlick. Additionally, advertisers receive the URL of the page you were on when you click on an ad on ITQlick. ITQlick also receives the internet protocol (“IP”) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, email patterns, your mobile device (including your UDID) and mobile operating system (if you are accessing ITQlick using a mobile device), as well as the name of your ISP or your mobile carrier. ITQlick may also receive location data passed to it from third-party services or GPS-enabled devices that you have enabled. Also, as described above in Sections 1.E. and 1.F., ITQlick receives information when you access web pages containing ITQlick interactive plugins. The link between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties without your permission, except as described in Section 2.L (“Compliance with Legal Process”), below.

#### J. Rights to Access, Correct and Eliminate Information About You

You have a right to access, modify, correct and eliminate the data you supplied to ITQlick. If you update any of your information, we may keep a copy of the information that you originally provided to us in our archives for uses documented in this policy. You may request deletion of your information at any time by 

 _[contacting ITQlick customer service](https://www.itqlick.com/)_

. We will respond to your request within 30 days. Please note, however that information you have shared with others, or that other Users have copied, may also remain visible even if you request its deletion.

#### K. Data Retention

ITQlick will retain your information for so long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, except in the case of our professional plugin impression data, which we de-identify after 12 months. If you wish to [close your account, you may do sohere](https://www.itqlick.com/Close). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce this Agreement.

#### L. Pixel Tracking

IT Media may employ a common technique usually referred to as "pixel tracking" to measure the effectiveness of marketing and advertisements, as well as compile aggregate usage statistics. Pixel tracking, which may be used in connection with advertisements on other sites, on the Website or in e-mail messages, involves the use of pixel tags (also known as "clear gifs," "Web beacons" or "1-by-1 gifs") that are not visible to the user of the site and consist of a few lines of computer coding. For example, if you visit the Website from an advertisement on another site, the pixel tag will reference the cookie you received when you clicked on the advertisement. The pixel tag also may register this activity with a business partner to allow us to count the number of times or when an advertisement is accessed. This data is collected for use in our marketing and research. Personally identifiable information about you is not collected by pixel tracking, nor is any tracking information generated from the pixel tag allowed to be used for any other purpose other than to report Website activity to us.

#### M. Third Party Advertising

We use third-­‐party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

### 2\. Uses of personal information

PLEASE BE ADVISED THAT IT MEDIA LTD MAY PROVIDE CERTAIN INFORMATION YOU SUBMIT ON THE WEBSITE TO THIRD PARTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, YOUR NAME, ADDRESS, PHONE NUMBER AND E-MAIL ADDRESS SO THAT THEY MAY CONTACT YOU ABOUT THEIR OWN OR OTHERS' PRODUCTS, SERVICES, OFFERS AND PROMOTIONS.

Additionally, you may authorize us to share your e-mail address with our Affiliates business partners, and third parties, including vendors whose products are profiled on the Website. If you opt-in and/or receive an e-mail opt-in confirmation, our Affiliates and business partners and third parties may contact you via e-mail, U.S. post, and/or telephone with a variety of special promotions, offers, or other information that may be of interest to you.  
IT Media may share personally identifiable information with its Affiliates and business partners necessary to complete transactions as part of its standard business operations and to assist us in offering products or services to you.  
First, we may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, users of the Website, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. Second, we may disclose user information when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by applicable law.

#### A. Consent to ITQlick Processing Information About You

The information you provide to ITQlick may reveal, or allow others to identify, your nationality, ethnic origin, gender, age, and other aspects of your life. By providing information to us for the purposes of creating your User account or adding any additional details to your ITQlick profile, you are expressly and voluntarily accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and ITQlick’s User Agreement that allow ITQlick to process information about you. Supplying information to ITQlick, including any information deemed “sensitive” by applicable law, is entirely voluntary on your part. You have the right to withdraw your consent to ITQlick’s collection and processing of your information at any time, in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy and the User Agreement, by changing yourSettings, or by [closing your account](https://www.itqlick.com/Close), but please note that your withdrawal of consent will not be retroactive.

#### B. ITQlick Communications

As described in the User Agreement, we will communicate with you through email, notices posted on the ITQlick website, messages to your ITQlick inbox, or through other means available through the service, including mobile text messages. We may send you a series of emails that help inform new Users about the features of the Services, and we will also send you service messages relating to the functioning of the Services. We may also send you messages with promotional information directly or on behalf of our partners, unless you have opted out of receiving promotional information.  
You can change your e-mail and contact preferences at any time by logging into your account and changing your [settings](https://www.itqlick.com/) related to your email notification choices. If you wish, you can also opt-out of receiving promotional emails by sending a request to ITQlick customer service through our [customer service site](https://www.itqlick.com/).  
Please be aware that you cannot opt-out of receiving service messages from ITQlick. Also, if we send communications to you via the carrier service with which you have a mobile communications subscription or otherwise have access, you understand you will pay any service fees associated with your receipt of messages on your mobile device (including text messaging charges).

#### C. User Communications

Many communications you initiate through ITQlick (e.g., an invitation sent to a non-User) will list your primary email address and name in the header of the message. Messages you initiate may also provide aggregate information about your network (for instance how many people are in your network), but will not list the people to whom you’re directly connected. Other communications that you initiate through the ITQlick website, like a request for an introduction, will list your name as the initiator but will not include your personal email address contact information. 

#### D. Customized Content

We use information you provide to us (or to third parties with whom ITQlick offers combined services) to customize your experience on our website. For example, when you login to your account, we will display the names of new Users who have recently joined your network or recent status updates from your connections.

#### E. Sharing Information with Third Parties

ITQlick takes the privacy of our Users very seriously, and we do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to third parties, except as described in this policy. We will also not share other personal information not published to your profile or generated through engagement with other ITQlick services (Groups, Questions, Answers, Company Pages, Products Pages, etc.) without your explicit consent or to carry out your instructions (for example, to process payment information) unless, disclosure is reasonably necessary in our opinion to: (1) comply with legal process, including, but not limited to, civil and criminal subpoenas, court orders or other compulsory disclosures; (2) enforce this Agreement; (3) respond to claims of a violation of the rights of third parties, whether or not the third party is a User, individual, or government agency; (4) respond to customer service inquiries; or (5) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of ITQlick, our Users or the public.  
ITQlick offers a “public profile” feature that allows Users to publish portions of their ITQlick profile to the public internet. This public profile will be crawled by and displayed through search engines when someone searches for your name. You may opt-out of this feature by editing your account settings; however, ITQlick does not warrant how often third-party search engines will update their caches, which may contain old public profile information.  
Content distributed through ITQlick’s sharing features and third party integrations may result in displaying some of your information outside of ITQlick. For example, when you post content to an ITQlick project that is open for public discussion, your content, including your name as the contributor, may be displayed in search engine results. Or, if you have bound your ITQlick account to your Twitter account, FaceBook account, LinkedIn account, Google + account, you can easily share content into ITQlick as well as to Twitter, FaceBook, LinkedIn and Google +.  
We may provide aggregated anonymous data about the usage of the Services to third parties for purposes that we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate, including to prospective advertisers on ITQlick.

#### F. Polls and Surveys

Polls and Surveys may be conducted by ITQlick, ITQlick Users or third parties. As a User, you may be invited to participate in polls and surveys from the ITQlick website. Your selection may be random, or it may be based on your non-personally identifiable information, such as job title, geography, products, company size and/or industry. Whether or not you decide to participate in a poll or survey is completely up to you.  
After you complete a poll, you will be given access to the aggregate responses of the poll on a results page. Some third parties may target advertisements to you on the results page based on your answers in the poll. Further, ITQlick or third parties may follow up with you via ITQlickMail regarding your participation unless you have opted out of receiving ITQlickMail messages.  
We may use third parties to deliver incentives to you to participate in surveys or polls. If the delivery of incentives requires your contact information, you may be asked to provide personally identifiable information to the third party fulfilling the incentive offer, which will only be used for the purpose of delivering incentives and/or verifying your contact information. It is up to you whether you provide this information, or whether you desire to take advantage of an incentive.  
We will not disclose any personally identifiable information to any third parties in connection with the conduct of any polls or surveys. Your consent to use any personally identifiable information for the purposes set forth in the poll or survey will be explicitly requested by the party conducting it. You may opt-out of participating in Surveys by changing your [settings](https://www.itqlick.com/) to stop receiving these inquiries and requests.

#### G. Search

We offer search services to help find information and learn more about other Users (for example, you can search for Users with particular expertise or consulting experience, or that you may know from your industry or profession), as well as projects, questions, companies, products and employment opportunities. We use information from User profiles and contributions to Groups, Projects, Company Pages, and Answers to inform and refine our search service.  
Questions, Answers, projects, and other Services. If you post on the Answers section of ITQlick, participate in ITQlick projects or groups, or import a blog, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you choose to provide there can be read, collected, or used by other Users of these forums, as well as Platform Developers and other third parties, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. ITQlick is not responsible for the information you choose to submit in these forums. Also, some content in ITQlick Groups may be public and searchable on the internet if the Group owner has opened the group for public discussions. You can delete your posts to Answers and ITQlick Groups at any time. However, please note that ideas you post and information you share may be seen and used by other Users, and ITQlick cannot guarantee that other Users have not made copies of or use the ideas and information that you share with others on ITQlick.

#### H. Testimonials and Advertisements Placed through ITQlick Ads Service

If you provide any testimonials about the ITQlick Services or place advertisements through the ITQlick Ads, we may post those testimonials and examples of advertisements you place in connection with our promotion of these services to third parties. Testimonials and advertisements may include your name and other personal information that you have provided.

#### I. Advertising and Endorsements on ITQlick

In order to deliver relevant and valuable ads to you and your network, ITQlick may use your name and profile photo in connection with social advertising based on content shared on ITQlick. This advertising may include the fact that you have recommended or endorsed a product or service on ITQlick, followed a company, joined Groups or conversations, established or added content to your profile, etc., and will only be displayed to your ITQlick network. You can opt-out of allowing your name and/or profile photo to be used in your settings.

#### J. Compliance with Legal Process

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information, profile information and/or information about your activities as an ITQlick User when required by subpoena or other legal process, or if ITQlick has a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (a) investigate, prevent or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities or to assist government enforcement agencies; (b) to enforce the User Agreement, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations, or to protect the security or integrity of our site; and/or (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property or personal safety of ITQlick, our Users, employees, or others.  
Disclosures to Others as the Result of a Change in Control or Sale of ITQlick Corporation We may also disclose your personal information and other information you provide to another third party as part of a sale of the assets of ITQlick Corporation, a subsidiary or division, or as the result of a change in control of the company. Any third party to which ITQlick transfers or sells ITQlick’s assets will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that you provide to us.

### 3\. Your Information Choices

#### A. Accessing and Changing Your Account Information

You can review the personal information you provided to us and make any desired changes to the information you publish, or to the settings for your ITQlick account including your email and contact preferences, at any time by logging in toyour accounton the ITQlick website. Please be aware that even after your request for a change is processed, ITQlick may, for a time, retain residual information about you in its backup and/or archival copies of its database.

#### B. Default Settings

Because the mission of ITQlick is to connect the world’s technology professionals to enable them to become more productive and successful, we have established what we believe to be reasonable default settings that we have found most professionals desire. Because Users may use and interact with ITQlick in a variety of ways, and because those uses may change over time, we designed our settings to provide our users granular control over the information they share. We encourage our Users to review their account settings and adjust them in accordance with their preferences.  
ITQlick accounts are also defaulted to allow Users to be contacted to participate in polls, surveys and partner advertising.

#### C. Closing Your Account

You can close your account through the ITQlick customer service site. If you close your ITQlick account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable database. If you close your account, we have no obligation to retain your information, and may delete any or all of your account information without liability. However, we may retain certain data contributed by you if ITQlick believes it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. ITQlick may also retain and use your information if necessary to provide the Services to other Users. For example, just as an email you may send to another person through an email service provider resides in that person’s inbox even after you delete it from your sent files or close your account, emails or ITQlickMails you send on ITQlick to other Users, as well as your contributions to ITQlick Answers or Groups, may remain visible to others after you have closed your account. Similarly, other information you have shared with others, or that other Users have copied, may also remain visible. ITQlick disclaims any liability in relation to the deletion or retention (subject to the terms herein) of information or any obligation not to delete the information. ITQlick does not control when search engines update their cache, which may contain certain public profile information that has since been removed from ITQlick’s publicly viewable database.

#### D. Memorializing Accounts

If we learn that a User is deceased, we may memorialize the User’s account. In these cases we may restrict profile access, remove messaging functionality, and close an account if we receive a formal request from the User’s next of kin or other proper legal request to do so.

### 4\. Your Obligations

As a User, you have certain obligations to other Users. Some of these obligations are imposed by applicable law and regulations, and others have become commonplace in user-friendly communities of like-minded members such as ITQlick:  

  * You must, at all times, abide by the terms and conditions of the then-current Privacy Policy and User Agreement. This includes respecting all intellectual property rights that may belong to third parties (such as trademarks or photographs).

  * You must not download or otherwise disseminate any information that may be deemed to be injurious, violent, offensive, racist or xenophobic, or which may otherwise violate the purpose and spirit of ITQlick and its community of Users.

  * You must not provide to ITQlick and/or other Users information that you believe might be injurious or detrimental to your person or to your professional or social status.

  * You must keep your username and password confidential and not share it with others.
  
Any violation of these guidelines may lead to the restriction, suspension or termination of your account at the sole discretion of ITQlick.  

### 5\. Important information

Children and Minors. Children under the age of 18 are not eligible to use our service.

### 6\. Security

In order to help secure your personal information, access to your data on ITQlick is password-protected. To protect any data you store on our servers, ITQlick also regularly audits its system for possible vulnerabilities and attacks, and we use a tier-one secured-access data center. However, since the internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to ITQlick. There is no guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. It is your responsibility to protect the security of your login information. Please note that emails, instant messaging, and similar means of communication with other Users of ITQlick are not encrypted, and we strongly advise you not to communicate any confidential information through these means.

### 7\. Your European Privacy Rights Under GDPR

If you reside or otherwise find yourself in the territory of Europe, we are committed to facilitate the exercise of your rights granted by the EU General Data Protection Regulation. Otherwise If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us using the button on the bottom "feedback & support".

#### Privacy rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation include:

  * Transparency and the right to information
Go over this policy in order to learn how we use and share your information. questions? contact us here: info@ITQlick.com 
  * Right of access, objection, restriction of processing, erasure, and portability.
You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time when we process your personal data based on your consent. To exercise these rights, please contact us: info@itqlick.com 
  * Right to opt-out to direct marketing.
Currently we don't use direct marketing, however, if we do you always have the right to opt-out at any time to receiving marketing materials from us using the instructions on the email or by contacting us: info@itqlick.com 
  * Right not to be subject to an automated decision, including profiling.
We do not make automated decisions using your personal data that may negatively impact you. We use cookies and similar technologies on our Site to personalize your experience on the Site and recommending software products and services that may be of interest to you. For additional information or to opt-out see our Cookie Policy. contact us with more questions: info@itqlick.com 

### 8\. How to contact us

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us using the button on the bottom "feedback & support". or email us at info@itqlick.com

© ITQlick.com 2012 - 2019 All Rights Reserved
